Isaya Bendera

<u>isayaelib@gmail.com</u> • <u>+255 684695157</u> <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/isaya-bendera-54b561190/</u> • <u>https://github.com/isayaeli</u>

Summary

Software developer with 4 years of experience in both mobile app development and website development, integration as well as maintaining soft wares. I have full-stack skills in both mobile and web development, looking to get a job at a company that will utilize my skills for the better Graduated with Bachelor degree in information technology from National Institute of Transport Tanzania,

Skills

Python • JavaScript • Flutter • HTML5 • CSS3

Work Experience

Full stack developer Jan 2021 – present

Ennovatehub • Full-time

Dar es slaam, Tanzania

Technologies: JavaScript • Flutter • HTML/CSS • Python/django • mySQL/PostgreSQL

Since 2021 to present, I have served as a full stack software engineer at ennovateventures, where I have been repeatedly recognized for developing innovative solutions for business, I am responsible for full life-cycle development of next-generation software, from initial requirement gathering to design, coding, testing, documentation and implementation. Known for excellent client-facing skills, I have participated in proposals and presentations that have landed six-figure contracts.

Projects

<u>Plumar</u> Jun 2021 - Sep 2021 • 3 mos

2 coworkers

Technologies: Python • JavaScript • HTML5 • CSS3

Plumar is talent training and hiring platform where by student have to learn get plumar certified and then get listed for employment, this platform is geared toward startup companies to help them get right talent without the hustle

Afrogulio Jan 2021 – present

1 coworker

Technologies: Python • django • JavaScript • HTML5 • CSS3

Afrogulio is a B2B e commerce site for selling processed good from other businesses, am currently working on it hopping to get done with it at the end of this month

crowedimpact Mar 2022 – present

1 coworker

Technologies: Python • Django • JavaScript • HTML5 • CSS3

Crowdimpact is a fundraising platform created for startups/SMEs to share their projects and donors to donate if they are interested by startups projects. Or in other words it is a platform to connect startups to donors funds, it is one of the project i have been working on since march.

TYVA(Tanzania Youth Vision Association) Project Management Tool

Jan 2021 - Apr 2021 • 3 mos

2 coworkers

Technologies: Python • JavaScript • HTML5 • CSS3 • Django

This is a tracking tool for youth association in tanzania which was created to help their organization to manage their project and to easly keep track of employees asigned task in the system

kaziconnect

Apr 2021 - Jun 2021 • 2 mos

2 coworkers

Technologies: Python • JavaScript • Django • HTML5 • CSS3

kaziconnect is a job portal where by employers post their jobs and candidates applies for jobs, it aims to give connect jobseekers to employment and give employers the right employee

smartgenge Aug 2018 – Oct 2018 • 2 mos

1 coworker

Technologies: Python • JavaScript • HTML5 • CSS3 • Django

smartgenge is an C2B e-commerce site for selling vegies directly to custerms

Educations

Bachelor's degree: Information Technology

Dec 2016 - Dec 2019 • 3 yrs

National Institute of Transport in Tanzania

Dar es slaam,

Grade/GPA: 2.8

Graduated at National Institute of Transport in Tanzania Bachelor degree in Information Technology-Language this is where i got serious with programming and invested all efforts i software engineering side of my studies

Certifications & Awards

Bachelor Degree in Information technology - Nationa Institute Of Transport in Tanzania

Dec 2019

Languages

English (Professional working proficiency)